A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller papers FA002
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Financial Materials, F; 400 linear feet
  - Charities Index Cards, 1863-1903; V14; 9 boxes
    - Cleveland Fund for Crippled Children - $200.00, 1900-1901 (Box 2, Folder 321)
      Goulder, Mrs. Mary R.
    - Cleveland Grays - $1,310.00, 1889-1893 (Box 2, Folder 322)
      Gardner, George W. Severance, L. H.
    - Cleveland High School - $1,084.85, 1898-1901 (Box 2, Folder 323)
      Cowles, J. G. W. Harris, E. L. Roberts, Jennie
    - Cleveland Homeopathic College - $17,000.00, 1891-1896 (Box 2, Folder 324)
      Biggar, Dr. H. F. Warmington, George H.
    - Cleveland Humane Society - $2,055.00, 1881-1893 (Box 2, Folder 325)
      Eells, H. P. Mrs. Graft Pennington, B. L.
    - Cleveland Huron Street Hospital - $5,200.00, 1899-1901 (Box 2, Folder 326)
      Waite, Mrs. F. P. Webber, W. H. (treas.)
    - Cleveland Infants Rest - $50.00, 1891 (Box 2, Folder 327)
      Edwards, Miss Lucia
    - Cleveland Loan Exhibition (relief of poor) - $200.00, 1894-1895 (Box 2, Folder 328)
      Covert, Jno C.
    - Cleveland Maternity Home - $1,275.00, 1891-1902 (Box 2, Folder 329)
      Bowers, Mrs. B. F. Carpenter, Mrs. A. G. Phillips, Mrs. W. A. Striebinger, Mrs. M. Watterson, Mrs. M. G.
    - Cleveland Men's Home - $450.00, 1893, 1896 (Box 2, Folder 330)
      Rudd, W. C.
    - Cleveland Municipal Association - $750.00, 1899-1900 (Box 2, Folder 331)
      Cowles, J. G. W.
    - Cleveland Normal Training School (for library), 50.00 (Box 2, Folder 332)
      Touzeau, Miss A. L.
    - Cleveland Orphan Asylum - $83.20, 1869-1870, 1881 (Box 2, Folder 333)
      Erie Street Baptist Church Sterling and Company
    - Cleveland Parks - $183,797.50, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 334)
    - Cleveland Philharmonic Orchestra - $300.00, 1892 (Box 2, Folder 335)
      Herrick, Myron T. Schroeder, W. A.
    - Cleveland Police Pension Fund - $50.00, 1898 (Box 2, Folder 336)
      Comer, George E.
    - Cleveland Public School (Art Education Society) - $600.00, 1898-1899 (Box 2, Folder 337)
      Davis, Miss E. C. Miss Etzensperger
    - Cleveland Quintette Club - $25.00, 1892 (Box 2, Folder 338)
      Unertz, Miss Marguerite
    - Cleveland Sabbath Commission - $50.00, 1881 (Box 2, Folder 339)
    - Cleveland Sunday Union - $200.00, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 340)
      Jackson, Rev. Alex
    - Cleveland Training School - $1,000.00, 1885-1886 (Box 2, Folder 341)
      Webster, J. H. Williams, E. P.
    - Cleveland Tunnel Disaster - $50.00, 1898 (Box 2, Folder 342)
      Hill, T. W.
    - Cleveland Vocal Society - $2,210.00, 1891-1901 (Box 2, Folder 343)
      Arthur, Mrs. A. Derricks, F. J. Kinsey, W. H. McCoy, F. W. Osborn, Mrs. L. A.
    - Cleveland World - $500.00, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 344)
    - Mrs. Clifton - $21.50, 1891 (Box 2, Folder 345)
      Mrs. Moore
    - Clinton College, Kentucky - $650.00, 1887, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 346)
      Hicks, Miss A. M. Leonard, Miss Georgia F.
      See also American Baptist Education Society - Clinton College.
    - Clough, Rev. John E. (Telgu missionary) - $3,250.00, 1884, 1891, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 347)
    - Clough, Mrs. John E. (education for daughters) - $3,030.00, 1886-1892 (Box 2, Folder 348)
    - Cobleskill Baptist Church - $100.00, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 349)
      Berry, Rev. J. M.
    - Cogbill, W. R. - $50.00, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 350)
    - Mrs. Cole - $25.00, 1891 (Box 2, Folder 351)
      King, Rev. G. O.
    - Cole, Austin H. - $20.00, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 352)
    - Coley, William B. - $500.00, 1901 (Box 2, Folder 353)
    - Collamer Episcopal Church - $325.00, 1896-1897 (Box 2, Folder 354)
      Smyth, P. Henry
    - Collamer Presbyterian Church - $700.00, 1894-1899 (Box 2, Folder 355)
      Hickox, Mrs. D. L. Merriam, J. B.
    - College Settlement, The - $900.00, 1901-1902 (Box 2, Folder 356)
      Stokes, Helen Williams, E. S.
    - Collins, Mrs. N. R. - $250.00, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 357)
    - Collinwood Chapel - $100.00, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 358)
      Stager, H. M.
    - Collinwood Congregational Church - $100.00, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 359)
      Teare, Mrs. Robert
    - Collinwood, Ohio Christian Church - $100.00, 1898 (Box 2, Folder 360)
      Beardsley, E.
    - Collinwood, Ohio Elections - $100.00, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 361)
      Humphrey, D. S.
    - Columbia University (New York City) - $110,500.00, 1899-1902 (Box 2, Folder 362)
      Low, Seth McNash, J. L. Seligman, Isaac
    - Columbia University (Washington, D.C.) - $250.00, 1899 (Box 2, Folder 363)
    - Comfort, Mrs. Lizzie J. - $50.00, 1896-1898 (Box 2, Folder 364)
    - Commercial Travellers Fair - $10.00, 1896 (Box 2, Folder 365)
    - Committee of Fifteen (New York) - $5,500.00, 1901 (Box 2, Folder 366)
      Baldwin, W. H. Jr. Orr, A. E. Smith, Charles Stewart
    - Comstock, Anthony (New York Society for the Suppression of Vice) - $1,450.00, 1894-1902 (Box 2, Folder 367)
      See also Society for the Suppression of Vice.
    - Congo Baptist Mission - $30.00, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 368)
    - Congregational Church on Heights - $10.00, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 369)
    - Congregational Missionary to Cala - $25.00, 1889 (Box 2, Folder 370)
      Miss Spelman
    - Conley, Paul (laborer's injuries) - $35.00, 1901 (Box 2, Folder 371)
      Hemenway, W. B. (hospital charges)
    - Conneaut, Ohio Bethel and Hospital - $500.00, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 372)
      McGean, J. A.
    - Connor, Mrs. (Forest Hill) - $105.00, 1892, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 373)
    - Conover, Hattie - $18.00, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 374)
      Hemenway, W. B. Jenkins, J. A.
    - Conwell, Rev. Dr. (Philadelphia) - $50.00, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 375)
    - Cook, Mrs. G. L. (Cleveland, Ohio) - $300.00, 1898-1900 (Box 2, Folder 376)
    - Cook, Homer N. - $30.00, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 377)
      Hulbert, E. B.
    - Cook Academy (Havanna, New York) - $4,000.00, 1884-1894 (Box 2, Folder 378)
      Fox, A. J. Freeman, A. L. Peters, T. R.
      See also American Baptist Education Society - Cook Academy.
    - Cooke, Mrs. Hattie E. - $95.00, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 379)
    - Cooke, Mrs. Rose Terry - $100.00, 1891 (Box 2, Folder 380)
    - Cookman's (Brother) Sunday School (German Baptist) - $179.85, 1864-1870 (Box 2, Folder 381)
    - Cooper, Peter Monument - $250.00, 1885 (Box 2, Folder 382)
      Grace, William R.
    - Cooper Union Employment Society - $200.00, 1895-1898 (Box 2, Folder 383)
      Faunce, Rev. W. H. P.
    - Corbett, John (Youth's Companion) - $1.75, 1901 (Box 2, Folder 384)
    - Corbett, Miss Manie (Harpers Young People) - $1.50, 1892 (Box 2, Folder 385)
    - Coren Student Hamilton (Education) - $50.00, 1885 (Box 2, Folder 386)
    - Cornell University - $250,000.00, 1902-1903 (Box 2, Folder 387)
      Williams, E. S.
    - Corning, New York Baptist Church - $500.00, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 388)
      Slocum, Prof. A. G.
    - Coshacton Baptist Church - $100.00, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 389)
    - Costello, Mollie (for Miss Sykes) - $100.00, 1895-1901 (Box 2, Folder 390)
    - Council Bluffs Baptist Church - $105.00, 1896 (Box 2, Folder 391)
    - Covert, John C. (campaign literature) - $100.00, 1896 (Box 2, Folder 392)
    - Cox, John H. - $50.00, 1895 (Box 2, Folder 393)
    - Crafts, Mrs. Sophia - $100.00, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 394)
    - Cramer, Rev. F. W. - $25.00, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 395)
    - Crandall, Rev. L. A. - $700.00, 1889-1891 (Box 3, Folder 396)
    - Crawford, Ohio Baptist Church - $100.00, 1886 (Box 3, Folder 397)
      Calhoun, S. L.
    - Cretan Refugees - $500.00, 1897 (Box 3, Folder 398)
      Woodward, James L.
    - Crowell, Mrs. E. - $50.00, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 399)
    - Crowl, Mrs. Edward - $25.00, 1893 (Box 3, Folder 400)
    - Cuban Orphans Fund - $2,000.00, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 401)
      Bacon, Robert
    - Cunningham, Eugene - $181.50, 1885-1889 (Box 3, Folder 402)
    - Curtis, Cicero B. - $1,750.00, 1892-1902 (Box 3, Folder 403)
    - Curtis, Mrs. I. G. (orchestra) - $12.00, 1891 (Box 3, Folder 404)
    - Curtis, Mrs. Mary (Owego, New York) - $50.00, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 405)
    - Cushing, C. W. - $100.00, 1879 (Box 3, Folder 406)
    - Cutler, Rev. Carrol - $600.00, 1886-1887 (Box 3, Folder 407)
    - Dakin, Mrs. H. E. - $150.00, 1887-1888 (Box 3, Folder 408)
    - Danbury Baptist Church - $15,602.41, 1902-1903 (Box 3, Folder 409)
      Biglow, L. H. Paddock, C. A.
    - Darlington, Wisconsin Baptist Church - $100.00, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 410)
      Adams, Mrs. Arthur
    - Darrow, Mrs. Elizabeth H. - $50.00, 1891 (Box 3, Folder 411)
    - Davidson, Charles - $10.00, 1890 (Box 3, Folder 412)
    - Davidson, E. (education) - $50.00, 1893 (Box 3, Folder 413)
    - Davidson, George - $100.00, 1881 (Box 3, Folder 414)
    - Davidson, Mrs. Minerva - $1,950.00, 1886-1901 (Box 3, Folder 415)
    - Davis, Miss E. C. - $275.00, 1888-1893 (Box 3, Folder 416)
    - Davis, Miss Minnie - $55.00, 1891, 1893 (Box 3, Folder 417)
    - Davison, John - $200.00, 1895-1897 (Box 3, Folder 418)
    - Davison, W. B. - $3.00, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 419)
    - Rev. Day - $10.00, 1863-1864 (Box 3, Folder 420)
    - Deaf and Blind Asylum - $25.00, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 421)
    - Deaf Mutes (church mission) - $30.00, 1886-1889 (Box 3, Folder 422)
    - Dean, George Hamilton - $200.00, 1895, 1897 (Box 3, Folder 423)
    - Deane, Jno. H. (painting of Dr. Anderson) - $50.00, 1883 (Box 3, Folder 424)
    - Deane, Mrs. Jno. H. - $1,000.00, 1891 (Box 3, Folder 425)
    - Decoration Day - $10.00, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 426)
    - Delaney, W. J. - $5.00, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 427)
    - Delvinatte, Theo. S. - $285.00, 1887, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 428)
    - Deming, May E. - $555.00, 1889-1892 (Box 3, Folder 429)
    - Deming, Mrs. M. R. - $100.00, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 430)
    - Deming, Rosett - $50.00, 1888, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 431)
    - Dennison University (Granville, Ohio) - $63,700.00, 1868-1900 (Box 3, Folder 432)
      Cranford, Z. Hoyt, J. M. Owens, A. Tuttle, Rev. H. H.
    - Denver, Colorado Baptist Church - $500.00, 1887 (Box 3, Folder 433)
      Cameron, Rev. Robert
    - DesMorets, Ernest A. - $285.00, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 434)
    - Detroit, Michigan German Baptist Church - $500.00, 1890 (Box 3, Folder 435)
      Otto, Rev. R.
    - Detroit Street Mission - $50.00, 1886-1887 (Box 3, Folder 436)
      Hoyt, Ida H.
    - Dickinson, Mrs. James S. - $100.00, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 437)
    - Diet Dispensary and Women's Ex. - $200.00, 1881-1884 (Box 3, Folder 438)
      Tuttle, Mrs. F. L. Tyler, W. S. Walton, Miss L. A.
    - Dixon, Rev. Joseph K. - $610.00, 1882-1895 (Box 3, Folder 439)
    - Dixon, Rev. Thomas Jr. - $2,250.00, 1896-1898 (Box 3, Folder 440)
    - Doan, Mrs. E. W. - $575.00, 1888-1895 (Box 3, Folder 441)
    - Dorr, Neal - Birthday - $25.00, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 442)
      Wordwell, W. T.
    - Dowknott, Mrs. George - $50.00, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 443)
    - Dowling, Miss M. A. - $250.00, 1890-1892 (Box 3, Folder 444)
    - Dowling, Mrs. George Thomas - $225.00, 1886-1894 (Box 3, Folder 445)
    - Dowling, Rev. George Thomas - $445.00, 1881-1885 (Box 3, Folder 446)
    - Downey, George D. (Miles City, Montana) - $1,250.00, 1885-1902 (Box 3, Folder 447)
    - Mr. Rev. Downey (Telgu Mission) - $500.25, 1856-1890 (Box 3, Folder 448)
      Coleman, E. P. Erie Street Baptist Church Johnson, Rev. G. J.
    - Downs, William F. (article in Journalist) - $50.00, 1888 (Box 3, Folder 449)
    - Dufl, Carl Concert - $25.00, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 450)
    - Duluth Bethel Association - $850.00, 1884-1898 (Box 3, Folder 451)
      Hanford, H. H. Sutter, Rev. C. C.
    - Duluth Hospital (St. Luke's) - $5,000.00, 1901 (Box 3, Folder 452)
      Morrison, Rt. Rev. J. D.
    - Duluth Second Baptist Church - $1,400.00, 1895, 1902 (Box 3, Folder 453)
      Lent, G.H.
    - Duluth Swedish Bethel Baptist Church - $500.00, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 454)
      Larson, Rev. M.
    - Duluth, Minnesota Sufferers by Fire - $100.00, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 455)
      Richardson, W. E.
    - Dumond (Tarrytown) - $25.00, 1902 (Box 3, Folder 456)
      Hemenway, C. K.
    - Duncan, Mrs. J. H. - $198.00, 1900-1902 (Box 3, Folder 457)
      Ballard, E. L.
    - Duncan, Mrs. S. W. - $500.00, 1881 (Box 3, Folder 458)
    - Duncan, Rev. S. W. - $500.00, 1885 (Box 3, Folder 459)
    - Duncan, Samuel W. - $300.00, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 460)
    - Dunham, Mrs. Mary Adams - $200.00, 1888-1890 (Box 3, Folder 461)
    - Dunkirk Baptist Church, First - $50.00, 1887 (Box 3, Folder 462)
      Raymond, Rev. F. B.
    - Durgin, George W. - $100.00, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 463)
    - Durling, Mrs. S. C. (Ladies Reading Room, Wadsworth, Ohio) - $100.00, 1902 (Box 3, Folder 464)
    - Dutton, Miss E. - $150.00, 1881-1882 (Box 3, Folder 465)
    - Dutton, Mrs. Emily A. - $700.00, 1896, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 466)
    - Dutton, Jennie - $20.00, 1893, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 467)
    - Duty, F. Jennie (presents) - $600.00, 1883-1891 (Box 3, Folder 468)
    - Duty, F. Jennie (salary as temperance worker) - $5,127.50, 1878-1895 (Box 3, Folder 469)
    - Earle, William - $225.00, 1885-1888 (Box 3, Folder 470)
    - East Baptist Church - $550.00, 1887-1889 (Box 3, Folder 471)
      Mosier, Rev. W. J.
    - East Cleveland Baptist Church - $25.00, 1901 (Box 3, Folder 472)
      Jenks, John J.
    - East Cleveland Methodist Church (Cleveland Ohio) - $200.00, 1886 (Box 3, Folder 473)
      Doan, Mrs. E. W.
    - East Cleveland Temperance Work - $6.17, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 474)
      Mrs. McCroskey
    - East Cleveland Volunteer Fire Department - $50.00, 1901 (Box 3, Folder 475)
      Walworth, F.
    - East End Baptist Church (Cleveland, Ohio) - $17,179.62, 1892-1903 (Box 3, Folder 476)
      Chubbock, S. E. Dawson, Thomas Gray, G. H. Morgan, C. J. Rockefeller, F.
    - East End Drill Corps - $10.00, 1888 (Box 3, Folder 477)
    - East Stroudsberg Baptist Church - $500.00, 1893 (Box 3, Folder 478)
      Baker, L. L.
    - Eaton, Rev. Charles A. - $700.00, 1902 (Box 3, Folder 479)
    - Education - $450.00, 1875, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 480)
    - Education - Colored Preachers and Teachers - $25.00, 1866 (Box 3, Folder 481)
    - Edwards, Anna (personal use) - $250.00, 1885-1891 (Box 3, Folder 482)
    - Edwards, Anna (salary, temperance worker) - $5,620.00, 1888-1903 (Box 3, Folder 483)
      Hays, J. L.
    - Egyptian Expedition Fund - $375.00, 1898-1899 (Box 3, Folder 484)
      Foster, F. C. Wilcox, Harold
    - Elberfield, Germany Baptist Church - $500.00, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 485)
      Bickel, Philip
    - Elder, Rev. Joseph - $500.00, 1902 (Box 3, Folder 486)
    - Eliza Jennings Home for Incurables (Cleveland, Ohio) - $15,993.39, 1889-1897 (Box 3, Folder 487)
      Mrs. Buel Buel, Rev. A. P.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
    - Elkhart, Indiana Baptist Church - $50.00, 1888 (Box 3, Folder 488)
      Chiltenden, Rev. George B.
    - Elm Hill Baptist Church - $100.00, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 489)
      Drew, Clara B.
    - Elyria, Ohio Baptist Church - $300.00, 1884 (Box 3, Folder 490)
      Bickford, C. R.
    - Emery, Miss Frances (for vacation) - $50.00, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 491)
    - Emmanuel Bethel Church (New York) - $1,283.52, 1886-1903 (Box 3, Folder 492)
      Ballard, E. S. Biglow, L. H. Bulnes, John Hansell, George H.
    - Emmons, Mrs. R. A. - $345.63, 1885-1894 (Box 3, Folder 493)
    - Engerd, W. A. - $25.00, 1891 (Box 3, Folder 494)
    - English, Rev. J. B. - $50.00, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 495)
    - Erie Avenue Baptist church (Cleveland, Ohio) - $4,964.40, 1883-1888 (Box 3, Folder 496)
      Hyde, G. A. King, Rev. G. O.
    - Erie Baptist Church (First Church) - $2,450.00, 1885-1892 (Box 3, Folder 497)
      Fox, E. F. Thomas, Rev. J. Cyrus
    - Erie Street Baptist Church Fair - $25.00, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 498)
    - Erie Street Baptist Church Pew Rent - $58.00, 1856, 1866 (Box 3, Folder 499)
    - Erie Street Baptist Church Piano - $20.00, 1865, 1866 (Box 3, Folder 500)
    - Erie Street Baptist Church Poor Fund - $66.92, 1856-1870 (Box 3, Folder 501)
    - Erie Street Baptist Church Subscription to Church - $1,610.07, 1856-1869 (Box 3, Folder 502)
    - Erie Street Baptist Church Sunday School - $182.51, 1864-1871 (Box 3, Folder 503)
    - Erie Street Baptist Church Sundry donations - $43,876.40, 1856-1878 (Box 3, Folder 504)
    - Erie Street Baptist Church Young Men's Fund - $39.00, 1863-1864 (Box 3, Folder 505)
    - Erie, Pennsylvania Kindergarten Work - $50.00, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 506)
      Black, Mrs. W. F.
    - Etzensperger, Miss Eliza (aid for young lady) - $34.50, 1889-1893 (Box 3, Folder 507)
    - Euclid Avenue Baptist Church (Cleveland, Ohio) - $172,662.04, 1880-1903 (Box 3, Folder 508)
      Adams, Charles E. Carvell, F. R. Mrs. Cook Davidson, C. A. Etzensperger, Eliza Holmles, C. R. Lang, C. F. Osborne, E. W. Reynolds, Iri Rudd, George A. Thomas, Ezra
      See also Second Baptist Church.
    - Euclid Avenue Baptist Church Ladies Society (Cleveland, Ohio) - $468.00, 1882-1890 (Box 3, Folder 509)
      Beach, Mrs. Clifton Thomas, Mrs. Ezra Urquhart, Mrs. William
    - Euclid Avenue Baptist Church Poor Fund - $1,242.60, 1882-1903 (Box 3, Folder 510)
    - Euclid Avenue Baptist Church Sexton (Cleveland, Ohio) - $60.00, 1888-1892 (Box 3, Folder 511)
    - Euclid Avenue Baptist Church Sunday School Orchestra (Cleveland, Ohio) - $949.50, 1883-1890 (Box 3, Folder 512)
      Amme, J. H.
    - Euclid Avenue Christian Church - $500.00, 1888 (Box 3, Folder 513)
      Alleman, Lottie J.
    - Euclid Avenue Congregational Church - $1,000.00, 1886-1887 (Box 3, Folder 514)
      Knight, T. S.
    - Euclid, Ohio Baptist Church - $500.00, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 515)
      Graham, Mary
    - Evangelical Alliance - $900.00, 1886-1896 (Box 3, Folder 516)
      Dodge, William E. Rowe, Caleb T. Strong, Josiah (secretary)
    - Evans City Baptist Church - $300.00, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 517)
      Ash, Joshua
    - Eveleth, Minnesota Holy Family Catholic Church - $250.00, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 518)
      McGoluck, Rev. James
    - Evening World Christmas Tree - $22.00, 1889, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 519)
      Mrs. Goodwin Stratten, Jno. C.
    - Evening World Sick Babies Fund - $25.00, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 520)
    - Everett, Washington Baptist Church - $80.00, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 521)
      Cooker, J. B.
    - Fairbanks, A. W. - $100.00, 1886 (Box 3, Folder 522)
    - Fairmont Methodist Church - $35.00, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 523)
      Rev. Askew
    - Faith House (New York) - $3,525.00, 1885-1898 (Box 3, Folder 524)
      Stebbins, Mrs. A. H. S. Strachan, Margaret
    - Fancher, Mollie - $10.00, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 525)
    - Farrar, Mrs. A. J. - $185.00, 1885-1886 (Box 3, Folder 526)
    - Faunce, Rev. W. H. P. - $3,128.44, 1890-1899 (Box 3, Folder 527)
    - Faunce, Mrs. W. H. P. - $1,700.50, 1893-1899 (Box 3, Folder 528)
    - Mrs. Faux - $150.00, 1901-1902 (Box 3, Folder 529)
      Bainbridge, Mrs. Lucy
    - Mrs. Featherstone - $747.50, 1868-1891 (Box 3, Folder 530)
    - Fenner, Mrs. Leonora - $1,000.00, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 531)
    - Ferris, Mrs. A. C. - $10.00, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 532)
    - Ferris, G. H. - $125.00, 1893-1894 (Box 3, Folder 533)
    - Fetzer, George - $400.00, 1884-1885 (Box 3, Folder 534)
      Deane, J. H.
    - Fiddis, Mrs. James R. - $100.00, 1901 (Box 3, Folder 535)
    - Fields, Miss A. M. (to publish book) - $50.00, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 536)
    - Fifteenth Regiment (Cleveland, Ohio) - $65.00, 1878-1879 (Box 3, Folder 537)
    - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - $53,214.54, 1867-1903 (Box 3, Folder 538)
      Allen, Mrs. S. F. Ballard, E. S. Comey, H. G. Denel, Mrs. J. M. Dr. Fagnani Dr. Gunning Hansel, George H. Kemp, G. M. Kulkhof, A. Marsten, E. L. Richardson, W. S.
    - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church Bible Class - The Club - $577.30, 1902-1903 (Box 3, Folder 539)
      Black, H. A. Clark, A. R. Dunn, B. S.
    - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church Ladies Society - $157.12, 1887-1890 (Box 3, Folder 540)
      Mrs. Faunce Hornby, Mrs. A. Scribner, Mrs. M. A.
    - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church Parsonage - $1,000.00, 1883 (Box 3, Folder 541)
      Goodwin, Charles T.
    - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church Pew Rent - $160.00, 1879, 1893 (Box 3, Folder 542)
      Hansell, G. H.
    - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church Sexton - $5.00, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 543)
    - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church Sunday School - $25.00, 1882 (Box 3, Folder 544)
    - Fifth Infantry Encampment - $200.00, 1885-1886 (Box 3, Folder 545)
      Major Gibbons
    - Fifth Regiment Company A - $20.00, 1886-1888 (Box 3, Folder 546)
      Dalton, J. J.
    - Findlay, Samuel - $50.00, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 547)
    - Findlay, Ohio Baptist Church - $50.00, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 548)
      Hillman, F. H.
    - First Baptist Church, Cleveland, Ohio - $50.00, 1879 (Box 3, Folder 549)
    - First Cleveland Troop - $50.00, 1879 (Box 3, Folder 550)
    - Five Points Mission - $400.00, 1886-1888 (Box 3, Folder 551)
      Requa, Abram S. Skidmore, Mrs. H. B.
    - Flower Hospital (New York Stock Exchange bed for employees) - $100.00, 1902 (Box 3, Folder 552)
    - Flushing, Long Island Baptist Church - $500.00, 1889-1890 (Box 3, Folder 553)
      Morrison, William
    - Foote, Ella - $83.00, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 554)
    - Ford, Mrs. J. W. - $225.00, 1899-1901 (Box 3, Folder 555)
    - Foreign Missions - $278.70, 1856-1869 (Box 3, Folder 556)
    - Forest City Guards - $75.00, 1878-1879 (Box 3, Folder 557)
      Mather, S.
    - Forest Hill Fire (gifts to employees) - $26.50, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 558)
    - Forman, George F. - $100.00, 1880 (Box 3, Folder 559)
    - Forshay, Mrs. E. - $5.00, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 560)
    - Fort Dade Baptist Church - $50.00, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 561)
      Tuttle, Julia D.
    - Fort Valley High and Industrial School - $50.00, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 562)
    - Miss Foster - $725.00, 1893-1899 (Box 3, Folder 563)
    - Foster, Edith B. (Chicago) - $50.00, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 564)
      Mrs. Emory Foster
    - Foster, J. Ellen (temperance worker) - $5,136.80, 1884-1903 (Box 3, Folder 565)
    - Foster, Mrs. Emory - $25.00, 1893 (Box 3, Folder 566)
    - Frear, Mrs. Melissa - $700.00, 1892-1902 (Box 4, Folder 567)
      Frear, Maria
    - Free Union, Virginia Baptist Church - $50.00, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 568)
      Morton, Mrs. Jerry W.
    - Freedmen's Aid Commission - $51.00, 1863-1867 (Box 4, Folder 569)
    - Freedmen's Relief Association - $110.00, 1879, 1882 (Box 4, Folder 570)
      Ely, George H.
    - French, Mrs. Francis A. - $150.00, 1895-1897 (Box 4, Folder 571)
    - Frese, Andrew (Cleveland, Ohio) - $100.00, 1893 (Box 4, Folder 572)
    - Friendly Inn, Central (Cleveland, Ohio) - $14,484.68, 1879-1891 (Box 4, Folder 573)
      Keith, Mrs. Kate S. Perkins, Douglas Perkins, John Mrs. Prather
    - Friendly Inn, River Street (Cleveland, Ohio) - $325.00, 1879-1881 (Box 4, Folder 574)
      Coon, Mrs. Jno. Mrs. Smith
    - Friendly Inn, St. Clair Street (Cleveland, Ohio) - $50.00, 1879 (Box 4, Folder 575)
      Worthington, Mrs. George
    - Frost, Jennie L. - $78.50, 1886, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 576)
    - Mrs. Frost (Cleveland, Ohio) - $30.00, 1892 (Box 4, Folder 577)
    - Fullin, Justin D. - $133.33, 1886-1887 (Box 4, Folder 578)
    - Mrs. Gagnier - $155.00, 1890-1895 (Box 4, Folder 579)
      Mrs. Chandler
      See also Seaman, Mrs. H. S.
    - Gallapolis, Ohio Baptist Church - $500.00, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 580)
      Leonard, Rev. G. E.
    - Galveston, Texas Flood - $5,000.00, 1900 (Box 4, Folder 581)
      Stillman, James
    - Gambier College - $5.00, 1864 (Box 4, Folder 582)
    - Garfield Club - $25.00, 1886 (Box 4, Folder 583)
      McBride, Lee
    - Garfield Fund - $1,000.00, 1881 (Box 4, Folder 584)
    - Garfield Monument Fund - $1,020.00, 1882 (Box 4, Folder 585)
    - Garfield Obsequies - $250.00, 1881 (Box 4, Folder 586)
    - Miss Garlock - $1,445.00, 1884-1902 (Box 4, Folder 587)
      Chandler, G. H. Miss Gilbert Miss Nutt